Guide to the UTU Records
UTU Records
- "Agreement Between Metro-North and the United Transportation Union" (Box 40.2, Folder 1)
- The New York, Susquehanna and Western Railway Co. Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 2)
- Ogden Union Railway and Depot Co. Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 3)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 4)
- South Buffalo Railway Co. (Box 40.2, Folder 5)
- St. Louis Southwestern Railway Co. Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 6)
- Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Co. Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 7)
- Long Island Railroad Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 8)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Co. Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 9)
- LTV Corporation Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 10)
- Maine Central RR Co./ Portland Terminal Co. Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 11)
- Texas City Terminal Railway Co. Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 12)
- AMTRAK Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 13)
- Union Pacific RR Co. Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 14)
- Northeast Illinois Regional Commuter Railroad Corp. Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 15)
- Oregon Pacific and Eastern Railway Co. Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 16)
- Various Agreements with UTU and Employees (Box 40.2, Folder 17)
- Agreements K-Z (Box 40.2, Folder 18)
- Agreements Carrier Level (Box 40.2, Folder 19)
- BLE Agreements- 1982 (Box 40.2, Folder 20)
- Conrail (Box 40.2, Folder 21)
- Caboose Agreements (Box 40.2, Folder 22)
- Eastern, Western, Southeastern Carriers' Conference Comm. (Box 40.2, Folder 23)
- Kyle RR (Box 40.2, Folder 24)
- Nat'l Agreements- Holidays, Vacations (Box 40.2, Folder 25)
- (Box 40.2, Folder 26)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreements, 1973 (Box 40.3, Folder 1)
- National Railway Labor Conference Agreements (Box 40.3, Folder 2)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreements, 1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 3)
- "Agreement", 1981 (Box 40.3, Folder 4)
- National Carriers' Conference Agreements- 1982 (Box 40.3, Folder 5)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreements- 1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 6)
- Mediation Agreement, Case A-8830, 1972 (Box 40.3, Folder 7)
- Cabooses- Article X- 1982 (Box 40.3, Folder 8)
- National Carriers' Conference Agreement- 1975 (Box 40.3, Folder 9)
- National Carriers' Conference Agreement-1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 10)
- National Carriers' Conference Agreement- 1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 11)
- National Carriers' Conference Agreement- 1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 12)
- National Carriers' Conference Agreement- 1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 13)
- National Carriers' Conference Agreement- 1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 14)
- National Carriers' Conference Agreement- 1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 15)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- 1972 (Box 40.3, Folder 16)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- 1972 (Box 40.3, Folder 17)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- 1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 18)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- 1975 (Box 40.3, Folder 19)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- 1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 20)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- 1978 (Box 40.3, Folder 21)
- Training Agreement with National Carriers' Conference Committee (Box 40.3, Folder 22)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- April 27, 1973 (Box 40.3, Folder 23)
- Mediation Agreement with National Carriers' Conference Committee- Jan. 27, 1972 (Box 40.3, Folder 24)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- Oct. 31, 1985 (Box 40.3, Folder 25)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- Oct. 15, 1982 (Box 40.3, Folder 26)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- Oct. 31, 1985 (Box 40.3, Folder 27)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee Agreement- Oct. 31, 1985 (Box 40.3, Folder 28)
- Agreements Nat. Carriers' Conf. Comm. (Box 40.3, Folder 29)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee (Box 40.4, Folder 1)
- Untied Transportation Union National Agreement- Aug. 25, 1978 (Box 40.4, Folder 2)
- United Transportation Union National Agreement (Box 40.4, Folder 3)
- United Transportation Union National Agreement- Aug. 25, 1978 (Box 40.4, Folder 4)
- National Railroad Passenger Corp. (Box 40.4, Folder 5)
- Off-track Vehicle Injury Agreement (Box 40.4, Folder 6)
- Operating Vacation Agreement Synthesis (Box 40.4, Folder 7)
- Southern Pacific (Box 40.4, Folder 8)
- Engineer Agreements- Crew Consist (Box 40.4, Folder 9)
- Union Pacific RR Co. (Box 40.4, Folder 10)
- (Box 40.4, Folder 11)
- Bus Lines- Agreements, Disputes (Box 41, Folder 1)
- " In the Matter of the Closed Hearing of the Governor's Fact Finding Commission RE: Southern California Rapid Transit Labor Dispute- Vol. III" (Box 41, Folder 2)
- " In the Matter of the Closed Hearing of the Governor's Fact Finding Commission RE: Southern California Rapid Transit Labor Dispute- Vol. II" (Box 41, Folder 3)
- " In the Matter of the Closed Hearing of the Governor's Fact Finding Commission RE: Southern California Rapid Transit Labor Dispute- Vol. I" (Box 41, Folder 4)
- "Proposals for Contract between Southern California Rapid Transit District and UTU, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- "UTU Special" (Box 41, Folder 6)
- (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Agreements- School Bus Drivers (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Bus Driver Agreements (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Structure- FRA, DOT (Box 42, Folder 3)
- RLEA- 8/81, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- BLE Nat'l Transportation Policy (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Articles I-IV (Box 43, Folder 1)
- "Accounting Procedure and Instruction Manual for Boards of Trustees and Treasurers of All Locals" (Box 43, Folder 2)
- "Your Own Newsletter" (Box 43, Folder 3)
- "Working on the Railroad- Job Descriptions UTU (Box 43, Folder 4)
- "Working on the Railroad- Job Descriptions by the UTU" (Box 43, Folder 5)
- "Working on the Railroad- Job Descriptions- UTU" (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Accounting Procedure and Instruction Manual for Boards of Trustees and Treasurers of All Locals (Box 43, Folder 7)
- UTUIA Insurance Programs (Box 43, Folder 8)
- "Your Own Newsletter" (Box 43, Folder 9)
- "A Guidebook for Union Organizers" (Box 43, Folder 10)
- "Your Own Newsletter" (Box 43, Folder 11)
- "Accounting Procedure and Instruction Manual for Boards of Trustees and Treasurers of All Locals" (Box 43, Folder 12)
- UTU Voucher Disbursements (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Pro Forma Balance Sheet, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Employee Assistance Program Workshop- Instructor Manual (Box 43, Folder 15)
- General Chairman List, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- General Chairman List, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Investigations and Discipline (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Accounting Instructions and Reporting Procedures- workbook (Box 43, Folder 19)
- "The General Chairman and His World", 1974 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- UTU General Chairman's Study Program, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- UTU General Chairmen's Study Program, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- 1981 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- "UTU Grievance Handling by Local Chairmen" (Box 43.1, Folder 1)
- Synthesis of Operating Vacation Agreement, 1980 (Box 43.1, Folder 2)
- Accounting Instructions and Reporting Procedures- workbook (Box 43.1, Folder 3)
- UTU Grievance Handling by Local Chairmen (Box 43.1, Folder 4)
- Report of the Committee on Constitution Fourth Convention- 1983 (Box 43.1, Folder 5)
- UTU Grievance Handling by Local Chairmen (Box 43.1, Folder 6)
- Report on Committee Constitution Fourth Convention- 1983 (Box 43.1, Folder 7)
- "Articles of Incorporation and Constitution of United Transportation Union Insurance Association" (Box 43.1, Folder 8)
- "Accounting Procedure and Instruction Manual for Boards of trustees and Treasurers of All Locals" (Box 43.1, Folder 9)
- Article 18- Duties of a Comptroller (Box 43.1, Folder 10)
- "Group Insurance Plan" (Box 43.1, Folder 11)
- "UTU Grievance Handling by Local Chairmen" (Box 43.1, Folder 12)
- UTU Field Manual (Box 43.1, Folder 13)
- United Transportation Union Telephone Directory of International Officers and General Chairmen (Box 43.1, Folder 14)
- "The Union's Files- A Guide to Establishing an Effective Grievance Filing System" (Box 43.1, Folder 15)
- Accounting Instructions and Reporting Procedures, 1984 (Box 43.1, Folder 16)
- Accounting Instructions and Reporting Procedures- workbook, 1983 (Box 43.1, Folder 17)
- Accounting Instructions and Reporting Procedures- workbook, 1983 (Box 43.1, Folder 18)
- Accounting Instructions and Reporting Procedures- workbook, 1985 (Box 43.1, Folder 19)
- "Background- A Report from Headquarters" (Box 43.1, Folder 20)
- UTU Field Manual, 1975 (Box 43.1, Folder 21)
- UTU Field Manual, 1975 (Box 43.1, Folder 22)
- "Field Manual Appendix" (Box 43.1, Folder 23)
- "UTU Grievance Handling by Local Chairpersons" (Box 44, Folder 1)
- "UTU Grievance Handling by Local Chairpersons" (Box 44, Folder 2)
- "The UTU: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow" (Box 44, Folder 3)
- "The UTU: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow" (Box 44, Folder 4)
- What Every Member Should Know About Federal Railroad Safety Laws and Regulations, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Construction and Interpretation of Agreements (Box 44, Folder 6)
- "Getting a Message to Congress" (Box 44, Folder 7)
- "Getting a Message to Congress" (Box 44, Folder 8)
- What Every UTU Bus Driver Should Know About Federal Bus Safety Laws and Regulations, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- "People Helping People" (Box 44, Folder 10)
- "UTU Grievance Handling by Local Chairmen" (Box 44, Folder 11)
- "UTU Grievance Handling by Local Chairmen" (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Vol. 12 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Vol. 13 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Vol. 5 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Officer Information Series No. 10-79 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Report of the Board of Trustees of the United Transportation Union (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Basic Day and Seniority Rules (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Railroad Investigations and Discipline (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Interchange Movements (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Report of the Board of Directors (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Report of the Committee on International Officers' Reports, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Report of the Committee on International Officers' Reports, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Report of the Committee on Constitution, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- "What Every Member Should Know About Federal Railroad Safety Law and Regulations", 1983 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- "The Injured Man" (Box 44, Folder 26)
- "The Injured Man" (Box 44, Folder 27)
- "Construction and Interpretation of Agreements" (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Operation Red Block (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Background Reports (Box 44, Folder 30)
- "A Decade of Progress Through Unity" (Box 44, Folder 31)
- "An Interview With Fred A. Hardin International President", 1987 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- "Statement of Fred A. Harding" (Box 44, Folder 33)
- "Background" Vol. 1- Vol. 4, 1970-1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- "Background" Vol. 5- Vol. 9, 1974-1978 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- "Background" Vol. 10 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- "Background" Vol. 10 (Box 45.1, Folder 1)
- "Background" Vol. 11 (Box 45.1, Folder 2)
- "Background" Vol. 12 (Box 45.1, Folder 3)
- "Background" Vol. 13 (Box 45.1, Folder 4)
- "Background" Vol. 13 (Box 45.2, Folder 1)
- "Background" Vol. 14 (Box 45.2, Folder 2)
- "Background" Vol. 15 (Box 45.2, Folder 3)
- "Background" Vol. 14 (Box 45.3, Folder 1)
- "Background" Vol. 15 (Box 45.3, Folder 2)
- "Background" Vol. 16 (Box 45.3, Folder 3)
- "Background" Vol. 17 (Box 45.3, Folder 4)
- "Background" Vol. 18 (Box 45.3, Folder 5)
- "Background" Vol. 19 (Box 45.3, Folder 6)
- "Background" Vol. 20 (Box 45.3, Folder 7)
- "Background" Vol. 21 (Box 45.3, Folder 8)
- (Box 45.3, Folder 9)
- Monthly Reports of the General Secretary and Treasurer (Box 45.4, Folder 1)
- "UTU Canada News" (Box 45.4, Folder 2)
- "The Other Side of the Story" (Box 45.4, Folder 3)
- "Retiree News (UTU)" (Box 45.4, Folder 4)
- Ride On (Box 45.4, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous (Box 45.4, Folder 6)
- "Head End" Inc. (Box 45.4, Folder 7)
- "Train and Engine Service Employment", 1973 (Box 45.4, Folder 8)
- 1973 (Box 45.4, Folder 9)
- Posters/ Advertisements (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Members' Time Books (Box 46, Folder 2)
- UTU Insurance Association (Box 46, Folder 3)
- First Quarter 1981-Percent Change (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Motivations and Progress (Box 46, Folder 5)
- UTU Member Folder (Box 46, Folder 6)
- UTU Info Pamphlets (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Railway Maps (Box 46, Folder 8)
- UTU Member Packet (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Transportation and Energy (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Research and Schedule Dept. Records (Box 46, Folder 11)
- UTU Policy Guide (Box 46, Folder 12)
- UTU Field Manual (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Annual Statement of the United Transportation Union Insurance Association, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Proceedings of the Meeting Held in Las Vegas, Nevada, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- The Official Railway Guide (Box 46, Folder 16)
- UTU Reports (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Convention Rosters (1st-3rd) (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Promotional Pamphlets (Box 46, Folder 19)
- UTUIA (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Employee Assistance Programs (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Economic Advantages (Box 46, Folder 22)
- "Working on the Railroad"/ "People on the Move!" (Box 46, Folder 23)
- "The Handbook of Transportation in America" (Box 46, Folder 24)
- "The Pocket List of Railroad Officials" (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Decisions Rendered by Various Boards of Arbitration (Box 46, Folder 26)
- The Official Railway Guide (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Cleveland, Ohio Rate Book (Box 46, Folder 28)
- Locomotive Firemen (Box 46, Folder 29)
- Railway Employee Assistance Programs- Project Reap (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Your Future Deserves Decisions Based on Facts: You Deserve the Answers! (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Your Future Demands Decisions Based on Facts: You Deserve the Answers! (Box 46, Folder 32)
- Emergency Board 195 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- Emergency Board 195- Transcript of Presentations (Box 46, Folder 34)
- Emergency Board 195- Index of UTU Exhibits (Box 46, Folder 35)
- Cliff Merritt Coloring Books (Box 46, Folder 36)
- (Box 46, Folder 37)
- Index- Exhibit 14 (Box 46.1, Folder 1)
- Index- Exhibit 14 (Box 46.1, Folder 2)
- Region Two Mid-Atlantic Association (Box 46.1, Folder 3)
- (Box 46.1, Folder 3)
- Accounting Procedure and Instruction Manual (Box 46.1, Folder 4)
- "What it Means for Rail Labor to be Involved in the Employee Involvement Process" (Box 46.1, Folder 5)
- Railroads and the Energy Crisis (Box 46.1, Folder 6)
- (Box 46.1, Folder 7)
- Directory- International Officers, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1970 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1971 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1975 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1976 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1977 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1978 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1979 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1980 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1981 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- "United Transportation Union Telephone Directory of International Officers and General Chairmen", 1982 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1982 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1983 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- "United Transportation Union Telephone Directory of Internationals Officers and General Chairmen" (Box 47, Folder 15)
- "Directory- International Headquarters and Locals", 1986 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- "United Transportation Union Research and Schedule Department Telephone Directory of International Officers and General Chairmen", 1984 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- "United Transportation Union Research and Schedule Department Telephone Directory of International Officers and General Chairmen", 1985 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- "United Transportation Union Research and Schedule Department General Chairperson Directory", 1985 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Directory of International Headquarters and Locals, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- "United Transportation Union Research and Schedule Department Telephone Directory of International Officers and General Chairpersons and State Directors" (Box 47, Folder 21)
- "Directory of International Headquarters and Locals", 1989 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- "Directory of International Headquarters and Locals", 1989 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- v, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- "Directory of International Headquarters and Locals", 1989 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- "Directory of International Headquarters and Locals", 1982 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- "United Transportation Union Research and Schedule Dept. Telephone Directory of International Officers and General Chairmen" (Box 48, Folder 5)
- "Directory of International Headquarters and Locals", 1984 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- "Directory of International Headquarters and Locals", 1985 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- "Directory of International Headquarters and Locals", 1987 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- "Directory of International Headquarters and Locals", 1988 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- "United Transportation Union Research and Schedule Department Directory of International Officers General Chairpersons and State Directors", 1988 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- "United Transportation Union Research and Schedule Department Directory of International Officers, General Chairpersons and State Directors", 1985 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- "United Transportation Union Telephone Directory of International Officers and General Chairmen", 1982 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- "United Transportation Union Research and Schedule Department Directory of International Officers, General Chairpersons and State Directors", 1985 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- "General Chairman List", 1982 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- "General Chairman List", 1981 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- "GCA Committees by Local, Title, and Amount of Assessment by Local" (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Job Banquet Appeal (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Case No. 84-1- Jacobs, Michael W., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Case No. 84-2- Sharp, Daniel J., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Case No. 84-3- Harvey, Kenneth J., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Case No. 84-40- Lasswell, Benjamin P., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Case No. 84-41- Bethel, R.L., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Case No. 84-42- Ottey, Orbie E., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Case No. 84-52- LeMier, James J., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Case No. 84-53- Garcia, Larry W., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Case No. 84-49- Ducey, Jack T., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Case No. 84-51- Clements, Ronald R., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Case No. 84-21- Harris, Albert G., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Case No. 84-22- Hernandez, D.F., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Case No. 84-23- Gormley, Charles F., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Case No. 84-24- Stevenson, Harold L., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Case No. 84-25- Ruth, Frank P., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Case No. 84-26- Vail, Jack F., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Case No. 84-27- Hammett, William D., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Case No. 84-28- Bridges, Ronald R., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Case No. 84-29- Goldsberry, Brad L., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Case No. 84-30- White, John A., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Case No. 84-31- Korn, David J., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Case No. 84-32- Cook, Vernon A., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Case No. 84-33- Miller, Lester, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Case No. 84-34- Lawhorn, WM. E., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Case No. 84-35- Geiser, Emanuel W., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Case No. 84-36- Sims, James L, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Case No. 84-37- Weltin, Joseph C., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Case No. 84-43- Lang, Robert C., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Case No. 84-44- Halley, Jack N., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Case No. 84-46- Schneider, James E., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Case No. 84-45- Latham, Edward F., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Case No. 84-4- Ivins, Thomas B., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- Case No. 84-5- Pelham, Daniel T., Jr., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Case No. 84-6- Barrier, Jeff M., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Case No. 84-7- Styles, Melvin W., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Case No. 84-8- Wheeler, Paul J., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 37)
- Case No. 84-9- Ballin, Michael J., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 38)
- Case No. 84-10- Williams, J.W., II, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Case No. 84-11- Shanks, Wm. D., Jr., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 40)
- Case No. 84-12- Trickle, John W., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 41)
- Case No. 84-13- Calvert, Paul C., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 42)
- Case No. 84-14- Harpole, Thomas E., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 43)
- Case No. 84-15- Winzer, Preston, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 44)
- Case No. 84-16- Raybourn, James e., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 45)
- Case No. 84-17- Smith, LaVorn, Sr., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 46)
- Case No. 84-18- Marietta, C.W., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 47)
- Case No. 84-19- Starks, Harold D., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 48)
- Case No. 84-20- Marcantel, Alvin E., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 49)
- Case No. 84-38- Ayer, Leroy, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 50)
- Case No. 84-39- Petit-Clerc, Lucien, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 51)
- Case No. 84-54- Cabana, Theodore C., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 52)
- Case No. 84-54- Coy, Richard W., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 53)
- 1984 (Box 49, Folder 54)
- Inventory of Memorabilia (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Photo Inventory (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Photo Descriptions (Box 51, Folder 2)
- (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Correspondence. General Project (Box 52, Folder 1)
- UTU Form Letters- '70-'71, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- A-B (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Francis Boardman- Legislative Director- NYS- Enginemen (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Louis J. Broten (Box 52, Folder 5)
- C-D (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Water Callies (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Walter H. Canty- General Chairman, UTU, Conductors (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Joseph Carberry (UROC) (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Willard W. Carson (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Charles J. Chamberlain (Pres, Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen) (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Al H. Chesser (Nat'l Legislative Director, UTU) (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Louis E. Chester (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Lov Chisholm (General Chairman) (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Daniel Collins (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Sal Criscione (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Thomas J. Duggan (Box 52, Folder 17)
- E-G (Box 52, Folder 18)
- G.R. Field (General Chairman) (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Henry Edwin Gilbert (Box 52, Folder 20)
- H-J (Box 52, Folder 21)
- M.W. Hampton- Milfred W. Hampton (Box 52, Folder 22)
- Edward Heisler- Sec. Right to Vote Committee (Box 52, Folder 23)
- J.P. Hiltz, Chairman National Railway Labor Conference (Box 52, Folder 24)
- K (Box 52, Folder 25)
- Jack Kaufman (Box 52, Folder 26)
- Roy Koepke (Box 52, Folder 27)
- L-M (Box 52, Folder 28)
- A.M. Lampley (Box 52, Folder 29)
- Clyde F. Lane- Former Pres, ORC+B, Asst. Pres, UTU (Box 52, Folder 30)
- O.R. Lundborg (Box 52, Folder 31)
- A.E. Lyon (Box 52, Folder 32)
- D.A. Miller- Chairman, Division I, NRAB (Box 52, Folder 33)
- F.C. Montgomery (Box 52, Folder 34)
- Harold Pryor (Box 52, Folder 35)
- O-P (Box 52, Folder 36)
- Leo M. Riley- Pres. UTU Local T-311 Mechanicville, NY (Box 52, Folder 37)
- G.W. Rogers (Box 52, Folder 38)
- R (Box 52, Folder 39)
- Ralph T. Seward (Box 52, Folder 40)
- J.L. Shattuck (Box 52, Folder 41)
- James Shultz (VP Public Relations, AAR) (Box 52, Folder 42)
- Charles J. Sludden (Box 52, Folder 43)
- Neil P. Speirs (Box 52, Folder 44)
- M.S. Stuckey (General Chairman) (Box 52, Folder 45)
- G.A. Stuebner (General Chairman) (Box 52, Folder 46)
- S (Box 52, Folder 47)
- T (Box 52, Folder 48)
- J.E. Wolfe, Former Head, National Railway Labor Committee (Box 52, Folder 49)
- W-Z (Box 52, Folder 50)
- Craft and Professional Employee Questionnaire (Box 52, Folder 51)
- Firemen-off Controversy, Spring- 1970 (Box 52, Folder 52)
- Local Union T-705 Syracuse, New York (Box 52, Folder 53)
- Fireman Manning Dispute (Box 52, Folder 54)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 52, Folder 55)
- Questionnaire for Railroad Union Local Chairmen (Box 52, Folder 56)
- Railroad Bibliography (Box 52, Folder 57)